Once you've done this, you can you'll
see this bright blue button pop up. Um,
this button in UX is called the happy
path. And in this case, you want to
follow the happy path. You want to click
the button that is demanding to be
clicked. Um, what it does is it takes
all of the copy code that you just
created here on your computer and um, it
allows you to push it to the remote
computer or in other words to push it to
GitHub. So, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to hit publish branch.
and it says you're going to need to log
in. So, I'm going to Okay. Um, once
you've successfully logged in, and some
of you may not have had that prompt,
depending on if you were logged into
your GitHub desktop already, you will
get this new happy path button that says
preview pull request. And you're going
to want to click that button. So, what a
pull request is is it says I have a copy
of my code and there's the main copy of
the code. I would like to take my code
and merge it in with the main copy of
the code. So I'm saying merge one commit
meaning the one thing that I committed
into the main code from the branch col
multiply function. And down here it says
it is able to be merged automatically.
So what you're going to do is you're
going to click create pull request.
When you do
it's going to open up your web browser
and it's going to bring in a title for
your pull request and you can add a
description. and you just want to say
what your code does. Um, once you've
done that, I'm here. I'm saying create a
multiply function takes two numbers and
multiplies them. You're going to hit
create pull request.
What this does is it checks that it can
merge with the base branch. If it can,
you'll get this nice green check mark
and there will be a button here that
says merge pull request. So if you are
working on a team, you don't want to
click merge pull request on your own
pull request. Uh you would want someone
else to look at the code for you. If you
are working by yourself, then you can go
ahead and click that button. Um but in
the next video, I will talk about how to
review a pull request from a different
account.